Bibek KC



info@kc-bibek.com.np



linkedin.com/in/bibek44



010-4881-2332



https://kc-bibek.com.np

Summary

I'm Bibek [Boy Is Bold, Easygoing & Kind]. I am interested in technology-oriented activities that use AI tools to solve any existing problems. With my 2 years of experience in diverse hands-on projects (https://kc-bibek.com.np/porfolio_bibek.pdf) and my enthusiasm for continuous learning, I am committed to pursuing new and challenging opportunities in the field of AI and deep learning, in order to expand my knowledge and skills in this rapidly-evolving domain. I am unikue [Undergraduate Nepali In KAIST Under Electrical-engineering]. For a quick and easy way to get information about me, try chatting with my chatbot at https://bibekbot.streamlit.app.

Experience



Research Intern

Robust Intelligence & Robotics Lab, KAIST

Jul 2022 - Dec 2022 (6 months)

Worked on developing a combined framework for realtime 6D Pose Estimation and Scene Graph Generation (SGG) in Robotic Manipulation Task. I used Cosypose framework for 6D pose and Neural Motif framework for SGG and performed experiments on custom cup datasets.

- For a single moving camera setup, estimated 6D pose and generated dynamic scene graphs.
- For 2 fixed camera setup, developed a probabilistic multi-view object-pose estimation framework that (i) associates multiple estimation results with scene graphs, (ii) combines pose distributions from single-view based estimators, and (iii) constructs a unified scene graph by predicting a unified pose distribution per object using MC dropout.

BISONAI

Backend Developer Intern

Bisonai

Jan 2022 - Feb 2022 (2 months)

- Built data pipelines (DAGs) in Airflow to collect DeFi data from various sources like Uniswap, Coingecko and stored them in MongoDB Atlas.
- Implemented backend API server using FastAPI and Strawberry (Python GraphQL Library) to provide DeFi data from MongoDB for users interested in knowing DeFi data from multiple Decentralized Exchanges.



Data Viz Project Intern

Interactive Computing Lab, KAIST

Jul 2021 - Aug 2021 (2 months)

 Made a course material for Data Visualization class i.e. a simple tutorial for visualizing plots with Vegalite and D3.js in Observable notebook for beginners to learn Data Viz techniques using Javascript.

Teacher Assistant

The British College, Kathmandu Jul 2017 - May 2018 (11 months) Conduct tutorial lectures and helping sessions- help/guide students if they have problem understanding any topics of the course (Chemistry, Physics, Mathematics and Biology)

Education



Fusemachines

Microdegree™, Artificial Intelligence 2023 - 2024

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology

Bachelors, Electrical Engineering and Computer Science Aug 2019 - Aug 2023

Tsinghua University

Global Summer School 2021, Al and Sustainable Development Goals Jun 2021 - Jul 2021

British Model College

High School Diploma, Chemistry, Biology, Physics, Mathematics 2015 - 2017

Skills

Python • Git • Robot Operating System (ROS) • C • Linux Server • Docker • Computer Vision • PyTorch • Vegalite, D3.js • Natural Language Processing (NLP)

Honors & Awards



KAIPlus+ Scholarship Award - KAIST

Apr 2023



Social Innovation Award - Tsinghua University

Jul 2021

KAIST International Student Scholarship - KAIST

Sep 2019



Country Topper in AS Level Chemistry - University of Cambridge

Nov 2016

Best student of the batch 2015/2017 - The British College, Kathmandu 2017

2nd Position in Inter-School Olympiad, 2016 - Budhanilkantha School